<Publish>
	<!--Id must be set in order to update existed mod. it is not required for publishing mod for the first time-->
	<ModId Value="" />
	<!--Name of the mod to display to players-->
	<DisplayName Value="City Services Redux" />
	<!--Short description of the mod-->
	<ShortDescription Value="Increases number of workers in City Services plus other small adjustments." />
	<!--Long description of the mod. Single line or multi line. Supports minimal markdown subset-->
	<!--LongDescription Value="Increases number of workers in City Services and other small adjustments." /-->
	<LongDescription>**City Services Redux** aka RealCity

Tweaks and modifies City Service buildings to your liking. By default, you could just install this mod and use it as-is with no configuration.

### Quick-Start
- Just Click "Use PRESETS" and play game, done.
- This has a curated preset list that increases the **number of workers** in a City Service (e.g., Central Intelligence) and a few other small adjustments (see below for details). 
- Number of configured buildings and extensions: **186**.
- Increased workers automatically increases the wages you pay per building (scaled by the game itself).
- New parameters are only applied to **new buildings**. 

### Power Users
- Also supports local configuration, so you can easily tweak the config file as you wish.
- If you want to change an existing building, it needs to be destroyed and plopped again to see changed employees or other values.
- DLC entries only work if you own the DLC and can plop the items.
- There is a separate Excel sheet that can generate road cost/maintenance entries; add the entries to the custom Config.xml for the mod to apply them.

### Features

* Curated Presets: all buildings have more workplaces and some have altered requirements for what education levels are required at that building.
All presets have been set manually taking into consideration various aspects. Some have only slightly more workers (2), but some have many more.
* Example: Central Intelligense vanilla is 100, the preset sets this to 300 workers for such a large building.
* Look into Config.xml or RealCity.log to find out about specific buildings, but you can increase or decrease what is in the preset file that comes with the mod.
* Crematorium has 2x higher processing rate to handle increased deaths from Population Rebalance (this won't matter if you use Magic Hearse).
* If you don't like the preset numbers, then use the player-modifiable local Config.xml (from ModsData/RealCity/Config.xml).
* New configuration can be applied/updated even during the game (use options menu).
* To add new components and parameters please refer to info and examples in Config.xml file which can be edited with Notepad++ or similar.

### Technical

* The mod does **not** modify savefiles or any game systems.
* Mod can be removed at any time. Already plopped buildings will retain modded params. New buildings will have ofc vanilla params.
* The configuration is applied during the mod initialization and after clicking **Apply Configuration** button. It is possible to apply a new configuration during the game.
* Performance: this is a lightweight configuration mod. It only does a short pass when applying settings (on game load or when you press APPLY). 
It does not add any per-frame systems, so it has essentially no impact on performance.


### CREDITS
- River-Mochi current author/maintainer
- Thanks to Infixo for the original City Services mod
- Fans of the mod who kept hope alive for a redux


	</LongDescription>
	<!--Thumbnail-->
	<Thumbnail Value="Properties/Thumbnail15.png" />
	<!--Screenshot, can be set multiple times-->
	<Screenshot Value="" />
	<!--Tag, can be set multiple times-->
	<Tag Value="Code Mod" />
	<!--Link to the forum post where the mod can be discussed-->
	<ForumLink Value="https://forum.paradoxplaza.com/forum/threads/city-services-rebalance-redux.1878625/" />
	<!--Version of the mod-->
	<ModVersion Value="0.5.0" />
	<!--Recommended version of the base game to use the mod-->
	<GameVersion Value="1.4.*" />
	<!--Dependency for the mod, can be set multiple times-->
	<Dependency Id="" />
	<!--Change log for new version. Single line or multi line. Supports minimal markdown subset-->
	<!--ChangeLog Value="" /-->
	<ChangeLog>
- complete refactor of the original
- updated to work for 1.4.* game patch
</ChangeLog>
	<!--External link. supported types are discord, github, youtube, twitch, x, paypal, patreon-->
	<ExternalLink Type="discord" Url="https://discord.gg/HTav7ARPs2" />
	<ExternalLink Type="github" Url="https://github.com/River-Mochi/CityServicesRedux" />

</Publish>
