<Publish>
	<!--Id must be set in order to update existed mod. it is not required for publishing mod for the first time-->
	<ModId Value="125675" />
	<!--Name of the mod to display to players-->
	<DisplayName Value="City Services Redux" />
	<!--Short description of the mod-->
	<ShortDescription Value="Increases number of workers in City Services plus other small adjustments." />
	<!--Long description of the mod. Single line or multi line. Supports minimal markdown subset-->
	<!--LongDescription Value="Increases number of workers in City Services and other small adjustments." /-->
	<LongDescription>**City Services Redux** aka RealCity

Tweak and modify City Service buildings to your liking. By default, you could just install this mod and use it as-is with no configuration.

### Quick-Start
- Just Click "PRESETS" and play game, done.
- Curated preset list that increases the **number of workers** in City Services and a few other small adjustments (details below). 
- Increased workers automatically increases the wages (scaled by the game itself).
- New parameters are only applied to **new buildings**.

Number of preset configured buildings and extensions: **186**.

### 6 Languages
* English, Français French, Deutsch German, Español Spanish
* 简体中文 Simplified Chinese, Português Brazilian

### Curated Presets
* All buildings have more workplaces, some have altered required education levels and other allowed tweaks.
* Presets were designed with various considerations. Some have only slightly more workers (2), and some have many.
* Examples: Central Intelligense vanilla is 200 workers, preset is 300 as this is a large building.
* Crematorium has 2x higher processing rate to handle increased deaths from Population Rebalance (this won't matter if you use Magic Hearse).
* Existing buildings need to be destroyed and plopped again to see changes for new values.
* If you want more than preset numbers, then see Power users.


### Power Users
- Easily tweak all player adjustable config file as you wish.
- Open mod options, then "Open folder" button to create a config file you can customize.
- Please refer to info / examples in Config.xml file for how to add / alter components (edit with Notepad++ or similar).
- New changes can be applied even during the game (use options menu).
- See Forum if interested in an Excel sheet helper that formats road cost/maintenance entries that can also be pasted into the config file.

### Technical

* DLC entries only work if you own the DLC and can plop the items.
* Safety: mod does **not** modify save files or any game systems.
* Can be removed at any time - already plopped buildings retain modded params and new buildings will have ofc vanilla params.
* Performance: this is a lightweight configuration mod. It only does a short pass when applying settings (on game load or when you press APPLY). 
It does not add any per-frame systems, so it has essentially no impact on performance.


### CREDITS
- River-Mochi current author and maintainer
- Thanks to Infixo for the original City Services mod
- Dorin made an excel file helper to create entries for road/maintenance costs
- Fans of the mod who kept hope alive


	</LongDescription>
	<!--Thumbnail-->
	<Thumbnail Value="Properties/Thumbnail10.png" />
	<!--Screenshot, can be set multiple times-->
	<Screenshot Value="Properties/10Actions.jpg" />
	<Screenshot Value="Properties/20CentralINT-Before.jpg" />
	<Screenshot Value="Properties/30CentralINT-After.jpg" />
	<Screenshot Value="Properties/40Actions-HowtoUse.jpg" />
	<Screenshot Value="Properties/50Actions-custom.jpg" />
	<Screenshot Value="Properties/70Actions-ZH-CN.jpg" />

	<!--Tag, can be set multiple times-->
	<Tag Value="Code Mod" />
	<!--Link to the forum post where the mod can be discussed-->
	<ForumLink Value="https://forum.paradoxplaza.com/forum/threads/city-services-rebalance-redux.1878625/" />
	<!--Version of the mod-->
	<ModVersion Value="0.5.2" />
	<!--Recommended version of the base game to use the mod-->
	<GameVersion Value="1.4.*" />
	<!--Dependency for the mod, can be set multiple times-->
	<Dependency Id="" />
	<!--Change log for new version. Single line or multi line. Supports minimal markdown subset-->
	<!--ChangeLog Value="" /-->
	<ChangeLog>
- fix images
</ChangeLog>
	<!--External link. supported types are discord, github, youtube, twitch, x, paypal, patreon-->
	<ExternalLink Type="discord" Url="https://discord.gg/HTav7ARPs2" />
	<ExternalLink Type="github" Url="https://github.com/River-Mochi/CityServicesRedux" />

</Publish>
