<Publish>
	<!--Id must be set in order to update existed mod. it is not required for publishing mod for the first time-->
	<ModId Value="125675" />
	<!--Name of the mod to display to players-->
	<DisplayName Value="Config-XML" />
	<!--Short description of the mod-->
	<ShortDescription Value="Increases number of workers and other small adjustments for Service Buildings." />
	<!--Long description of the mod. Single line or multi line. Supports minimal markdown subset-->
	<LongDescription>**Config-XML**

Tweak and modify Service buildings to your liking. By default, you could just install this mod and use it as-is with no configuration.

### Quick-Start

- ✅ Just select "PRESETS" and play, done (list of changes already included).
- Curated presets increase the **number of workers** and a few other small adjustments (details below).
- Wages are scaled up/down based on the number of workers - done automatically by the game (we just tweak worker counts).
- Think of this mod as a simple text-like file that players can edit (or not since a nice preset file is included).
- Change is applied before any city is loaded, so there is no performance impact.

Number of **preset** buildings and extensions: **222**.

### Curated Presets
- All buildings have more workplaces. The required education level for jobs is also adjusted in 'some' buildings, and other allowed tweaks.
- Presets design: some have only a few more workers (2), and some have many. This better utilizes large buildings that previously had few workers, and may help reduce unemployment.
- Examples: University is normally 170 workers, this mod preset increases it to 400 as this is a big campus for 15,000 students.
- Existing buildings need to be rebuilt to see new config changes.
		
- Add these companion mods to also <a href="https://mods.paradoxplaza.com/mods/123887/Windows">Increase Students</a> or <a href="https://mods.paradoxplaza.com/mods/123738/Windows">Transit Passengers</a>
- See Power Users if you want to adjust the presets yourself.

### Power Users
- Easily tweak all player adjustable config file as you wish.
- ✅ Open Options > Custom > [Open Config folder] to create a customizable Config.xml file.
- Refer to info / examples in Config.xml for how to add / alter components (edit with Notepad++ or similar).
- New changes can be "Applied" even during the game without a restart (options menu).

### Notes

- DLC entries only work if you own the DLC and can plop the items.
- Safety: mod does **not** modify save files or any game systems.
- Can be removed at any time - already plopped buildings retain modded values and new buildings will have vanilla values.
- Performance: this is a lightweight configuration mod. It only does a short pass when applying settings (on game load or when you click APPLY).
It does not add any per-frame systems, so it essentially has no impact on performance.
- Works with mods: Adjust School, Adjust Transit, <a href="https://mods.paradoxplaza.com/mods/125343/Windows">Magic Mail</a>, <a href="https://mods.paradoxplaza.com/mods/124159/Windows">Magic Garbage</a>, as this mod is focused on the number of workers and those do not.
- <a href="https://mods.paradoxplaza.com/mods/123497/Windows">Magic Hearse</a> and <a href="https://mods.paradoxplaza.com/mods/121256/Windows">Achievement Fixer</a> also works with this.
- Pretty much any mod that doesn't also adjust worker numbers should be good.
- Technically, this mod allows for virtually any changes to Service buildings. At the moment, it mainly increases number of workers
  in Services buildings and does other small adjustments. I encourage contribution to the mod and PRs on GitHub with proposed changes and rationale.

### 10 Languages
* English, Français French, Deutsch German, Español, Italian
* 简体中文 Simplified Chinese, Português Brazilian, Polski Polish
* 한국어 Korean, 日本語 Japanese, 繁體中文 Traditional Chinese

### CREDITS
- River-Mochi author
- Thanks to Infixo for original City Services Rebalance mod (retired)
- Fans of the mod who kept hope alive
- BugsyG, Dorin - testing

	</LongDescription>
	<!--Thumbnail-->
	<Thumbnail Value="Properties/Thumbnail10.jpg" />
	<!--Screenshot, can be set multiple times-->
	<Screenshot Value="Properties/10Actions.jpg" />
	<Screenshot Value="Properties/20CentralINT-Before.jpg" />
	<Screenshot Value="Properties/30CentralINT-After.jpg" />
	<Screenshot Value="Properties/40Actions-HowtoUse.jpg" />
	<Screenshot Value="Properties/50Actions-custom.jpg" />
	<Screenshot Value="Properties/70Actions-ZH-CN.jpg" />
	<Screenshot Value="Properties/80University.jpg" />

	<!--Tag, can be set multiple times-->
	<Tag Value="Code Mod" />
	<!--Link to the forum post where the mod can be discussed-->
	<ForumLink Value="https://forum.paradoxplaza.com/forum/threads/config-xml.1878625/" />
	<!--Version of the mod-->
	<ModVersion Value="0.7.0" />
	<!--Recommended version of the base game to use the mod-->
	<GameVersion Value="1.5.*" />
	<!--Dependency for the mod, can be set multiple times-->
	<Dependency Id="" />
	<!--Change log for new version. Single line or multi line. Supports minimal markdown subset-->
	<!--ChangeLog Value="" /-->
	<ChangeLog>
- added Japanese 日本語, 繁體中文 Traditional Chinese, and Italian
- New README file added next to Config.xml with updated usage notes.
- Renamed to **Config-XML**. One-time migration of any old **RealCity Config.xml** to the new **ConfigXML** folder.
- Refactor: improved Config.xml safety: auto repairs missing files with valid config, 
improved "Dump Status" button output, verbose log toggle not available in Release build. 
	</ChangeLog>
	<!--External link. supported types are discord, github, youtube, twitch, x, paypal, patreon-->
	<ExternalLink Type="discord" Url="https://discord.gg/HTav7ARPs2" />
	<ExternalLink Type="github" Url="https://github.com/River-Mochi/ConfigXML" />
</Publish>
